[Music]
have you ever seen the moon this full
it's a spectacle so bright and
beautiful I can feel it hiding something
more was inside before but knocking at
the door there's a deeper
side of me what a huge relief that you
can do the same when I could have been a
gentle man there's another friend they
tremble at my name we belong in the same
dark shadow cast the doubts and just
struggled away we can see who we are at
midnight more than we can in the day I
want you by my side more than a night
show me youron Power I
nice for such a brand new world as a
blooming fantasy we'll make history out
how will we know is more than just a
li has far beyond salvation dooming
fantasy only you and me